Fatwa Kurnia Budiman

West Java. Indonesia



fatwa.kurnia.budiman@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/fatwa-kurnia-budiman-645696141

Summary

Experienced Information Technology Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the oil & energy industry. Skilled in PHP, JavaScript, SQL, Linux, Python, Ruby, and Data Analysis. Strong information technology professional graduated from Gunadarma University.

Experience

IT Programmer

PT. Wiraswasta Gemilang Indonesia Nov 2018 - Present (3 years 1 month +)

Web Application Developer

Firmanlaw.com Oct 2021 - Present (2 months +)

Web Application Developer

Semuadikasih.com Nov 2017 - Nov 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Education



Gunadarma University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Informatics Engineering 2014 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



Sertifikat Kompetensi Pengembang Web Pratama - Badan Nasional Sertifikasi

Issued Apr 2018 - Expires Apr 2021 ICT 294 03184 2018

Digital Talent Scholarship: Data Analytics - Microsoft and online learning partnership between Ministry of Communications and Informatics

Skills

PHP • JavaScript • SQL • Data Analysis • HTML5 • Ruby • Python (Programming Language) • Linux Server • Linux • React.js